Thank you for watching!
Ending of "Hajime Shacho
Work fee What we do
For class of sewing services
Sorry, dealing with the variety skills
Yes, sir.
You all haven't eaten?
No, we're not eating.
Debbie Mayo's lutti.
Did you eat it by any chance?
It's my hair.
Uh, maybe.
I don't know.
It's just a circle.
Like this.
What? So maybe it's the other way around?
Last time I was in a radio booth.
Ukira was live, too.
Maybe it's because you said her hair is like this.
I think he means look at it like this.
That we're the audience.
I'm talking to a customer here.
I wonder what he's talking about today.
They're looking at you.
I'm such a beginner.
They're staring at me.
From here.
I'll tell you what.
Raffia.
I slept in.
But I'm a little nervous.
I don't know how long I'll be here.
I don't know yet.
I'm a little nervous.
But I'm not nervous.
Even on top of a big crowd.
I've got a mind that doesn't get nervous
I've got it.
Where are you from?
From home.
Ten billion points.
The new song.
Laughing.
As for Laughing.
I'm a little nervous
I'm a little nervous.
I slept really well
It's so cool!
I put on my own Simin and went to sleep.
self-symin
I slept just fine.
Slept well... about 10 hours.
I overslept
I'm not nervous yet.
Mr. Takama and Mr. Tokiho Cheng Award
Mr. Takama and Mr. Tokiho Chengsho said he's a great guy.
"People to the limit," they said.
I'm sure everyone has a lot of anxiety.
I'm sure everyone has a lot of anxieties, but
I'm more than that.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I've been practicing every day for a long time.
I've been practicing every day.
I'm going to perform it to the fullest.
That's how I feel.
I think there are a lot of people who don't know us
I think there are a lot of people who don't know about us.
I hope this will be an opportunity
I hope this will be an opportunity to spread the word
I hope it will be a good opportunity to spread the word
I'm more worried about whether it's going to be a good time or not.
I'm more worried about my nerves.
They don't know us at all.
So we have to turn them into fans.
But if we don't turn them into fans.
The number of fans won't increase.
To borrow a phrase from Mr. Sakama
A pinch is a chance.
It's like a pinch is an opportunity.It's like...
You're kidding.
I'm messing up.
Why?
Aren't you scared of standing in front of 10,000 people?
I'm scared.
I wonder how they'll react.
Where should I look?
It's been four years since I've been to an event I've enjoyed.
I don't want to be told what to think.
I don't want to create a weird atmosphere
I'm trying to read the atmosphere
I'm just trying to read the atmosphere and make it fun.
I can't sleep.
Mr. Tyson and the others are putting a lot of pressure on me.
I'm in front of 10,000 people.
I'm saying things like, "Hey...
I'm nervous.
I want all nine of us to be able to show our riffraff.
I want all nine of us to be able to show our Rough Ruffians.
I'm going to give it my all.
I'll do my best and make no mistakes.
Mr. Sakuma is our next guest.
Rough Ruffians!
And then...
I don't know which way he's going to come out.
I don't know which way they are
I'm in the middle of the room
I'm going to go in the middle.
Oh, no.
That's all right.
I'm not going to ask you to push me.
When this is in place.
I'm going to ask you to push it.
I think the sound is fine.
On the tension, it's in place.
In the swing...
Here's the song.
These are the debut songs that Mr. Sakama wrote lyrics for us.
Listen to them.
Ten billion points for ruff ruff ruff.
And it starts with a doon, so it's totally doable, right?
It's all right.
Are you okay, Mr. Natsumiya?
It's tough, but...
You will hear two songs.
The first one is...,
Please listen to it like this.
Congratulations.
Why don't you start with the second one? Okay, then.
Let's just walk to number 2,
Let's get excited.
Laughing as usual.
Coussie your hands.
I guess I'll go like this.
Thank you. Good luck.
Oh, I'm scared.
I didn't get to hear "ten billion points" one more time.
At the beginning of the raffing,
Rousing? I mean,
I'm supposed to be the one to do the
I managed to pull that off,
I'll try to make it in time.
Thank you.
Are you all right? Are all of you doing the exercises?
Yes, sir.
Did you all have a 10-billion-point day?
No, not 10 billion.
How were the 10 billion points? How were the 10 billion points?
How were 10 billion points? Next is a song that will make you smile.
Let's get excited. Laughing.
Oh, perfect.
Like at your debut live performance?
Yeah.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please do.
Nice to see you on new time.
Roger that.
Sorry about that. Thank you.Sorry. Thank you.
No, thank you. I'm sorry.
Whoo!
How's it going?
It was good.
Thank you very much.
It's cold!
Please.
Slow down and relax.
Oh, my God! I'm nervous.
Yes, it's bad.
I'm having an "ah-hum" moment.
Since a while ago. I've been so self-pitying since a while ago.
I'm sorry.
He was so cute. So cute.
He was cute.
I want to be like that.
Is your forehead showing?
My forehead is showing.
I thought I'd sweat anyway, so I gave it to him.
Are you giving it to him?
No, I didn't.
It's too wide.
Are you taking pictures?
It's been a while.
I think I just posted a picture on Twitter once.
I probably will.
I hope it's well received.
You have to say your name with your number.
It is well written.
Teacher.
Pleased to meet you.
Best regards.
Congratulations.
The best Iser.
Ten billion points, ten billion points already.
Now please listen to this, 10 billion points.
can't stop me, can't stop me
because I can see you.
HEY! LIE TO YOURSELF.
Thank you.
Rehearsal is over. I'll see you after this, please.
please.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Thank you very much.
That's not nice.
Oh, my God.
I'm scared.
When I looked at it like this, there were people all over.
I was afraid to look at them like this, so I just looked straight ahead.
But then I thought...
There were people who always come here.
I was happy to see some people I know.
I was happy to see them.
Just like Mr. Tae-penn was distracted.
There were people up to the limit of their eyes
I was really surprised!
I could see who was amazing.
I could see so well!
I wondered if they were all people.
I was a little bit surprised.
But I could see them.
Yoshimura...
I could see them.
I saw mine.
The Rough Riders...
You did a great job.
I feel relieved.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Please do
Let's have a proper party
Please doPlease.
Please, please, please, please.
Please, sir.
I'm begging you.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, I do.
I want Rachlaff to do well, but...
But first of all, I'm nervous.
I see.
He's a great guy.
Not so much.
Let's make sure it's a good time.
I'll do my best.
Do you have a plan for the talk?
No, I don't.
I don't even have a plan.
I don't even have one.
I don't want to be too specific.
It depends on what you're going to do.
I'll do my best.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [Music]
Today, my name is Sakuma, a Make Boy user.
My name is Nobuyuki Sakuma. I look forward to working with you.
Please do me a favor.
I'm going to give a special talk on Make-Boy's All Night Nick Hotel in Sakuma.
Thank you for coming.
Then don't stop.
I say don't stop radio.
Also, folks, I'm sure this is all over the Internet news.
We're doing another rehearsal here.
I'm going to go ask for your first reactions.
I'm sorry.
You and I, we first worked together about 8 years ago, right?
Yes, that's right.
It's like this.
I see.
That was when I...
Did you decide to mess with me, ghost?
I wasn't going to tease you.
But, you know, at that time, Yoshida recommended me for the upcoming breakthrough idol.
When we were on the move, I was told to get ready, and then Sakuma-san and others asked me to come.
I didn't want to do it that way.
So I thought, "Well, can we make it exciting? I would like to connect with them if I can, but
I'd like to connect with them if I can, but I'm not sure if they'll be excited about it. I think that's totally fine.
Uh...
Attentive and humble.
That someone's a little humble stunt.
I mean, there was a humble stunt.
in the song there or something like that.
Yeah, yeah.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
Are you nervous?
You'll still be warm.
You look so red.
Thank you very much.
Oh, don't be rough.
Oh, no. I'm making a slight mistake.
That's great, people.
Oh, great. You're speaking at the top of your lungs.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Are you cold?
It's cold.
It's gonna be hot.
Pon-chan first.
I would.
Thank you.
Tiny.
Thank you very much
Well, so, that's the end of Anochan's guest.
After this, I, Sakuma, will be the producer.
I, Sakuma, am the producer of this group.
This group is our guest.
They are all members of Ruff Ruff.
Please give them my best regards.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for having us.
I've only performed in front of 3 or 400 people,I've only played live in front of three or four hundred people,
I came to this site the following week,
We're all a little bit nervous,
Please introduce yourself.
Yes, let me introduce myself.
Interesting, interesting, interesting. We're all funny.
We're here to cheer you up.
Leave it to us.
Seino, I'm Ruff Ruff. Hello, Ruff Ruff.
Isn't this a surprising greeting for a first-time visitor?
I didn't come up with this. They thought of it.
If I had thought of it, I wouldn't have made them say such a scary greeting.
Oh, well, let's go a little further this way.
Let's go to zero.
Ah, yes.
I'm sorry. I'm really like an amateur.
I was standing in the middle of the room, at number zero,
I was standing at the number two position.
What do you mean?
I'm the closest person ever. What do you think?
I have never performed in front of such a large audience before,
We've never done it in front of such a large audience.
So now we look like potatoes.
How are we doing?
Well, it's more than the number of people at school.
That was a really, really shitty answer.
More than the number of people in the school?
Don't ever say that to Cocofest.
I won't.
Hibino, this girl named Hibino, she's been doing this since Seishun High School,
I've known her for about 6 years now.
That's right.
I don't think I've ever performed in front of such a big audience.
No, it's the first time.
And he's being watched.
I don't know how to say it. I'm too bad at it.
You are being watched.
You guys are on stage.
So, please do your best with the song introductions and everything.
Yes, I will. Thank you very much.
Mr. Sakuma, you've made us aware of this.
Oh, we?
Seriously?
It's fine.
You're cute.
She's cute.
Ideal.
Yes, so, I know many of you are new to this,
If you'd like, the weather is nice, so if you'd like, you can stay in the excitement.
The weather is good.
It's all about the weather.
It's nice.
Certainly. Please give me your best wishes.
Please do.
Let's listen to two songs in succession.
First, the debut song. The best present from Mr. Sakuma to us.
Now we will deliver it to you.
Please accept it.
Ten billion points for the riffraff.
Ten billion points. Ten billion points already.
I'll give it to you.
Ten billion points. Ten billion more points.
If you're alive now, you're already good.
Continually bound by the curses of others
How long are you going to stay down here?
Come on, the knife of carved words
I always forget
Hand in hand, hand in hand, it's really useless
For whom are love and laughter for?
I'll make you dirty, I'll make you proud, I'll make you proud
Impossible things only silly magic
Oh, look who's in pain
Let us just laugh and laugh
Let me dance Let me dance I'll take it back
Let me dance Let me dance Let me dance Let me dance
Let me dance Let me dance Even if I cry
You make me like you like you like you like you
Remember, more and more and more and more
Oh la la la la 50 billion points
Give it to yourselfI gave it to myself.
Ten billion points.
Said it again.
Good work.
Thanks for your hard work.
Have a great time.
Hey! Says when You sometimes mutter
Always when you lose sight of what's important.
All you think about is yourself.
Look up and unfold the map
Let's go greet the future
Dancing, Dancing, Dancing, Yeah
I only love this time
Hear how I'm feeling
Smile and say congratulations on everything
Cry to cry
Oi! Yay!
That's great.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for wanting to listen.
This is the most nerve-wracking part of the show.
I feel like a parent.
Do you have any advice
Ana, from your idol.
As a senior idol
As a senior
I will not be defeated by a strong authority.
Right away, you mean there's Kurumo who says I should be like this, right?
That's right, that's right. Ignore them!
Well, how was it with the members of the "ah hah hah hah" group?
It was fun.
I didn't expect so many people to come,
It was really my first time on stage,
Thank you very much for your kind attention.
Thank you very much.
Now, everyone, please come to the stage. I'm going to take a picture.
Okay, okay.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
See you on the radio.
I've been feeling really white and really excited. It's terrible.
There were so many people in the audience, but I said some incomprehensible things.
I regret so much that I couldn't speak properly.
I did it this time.
That's pretty much it.
I made a mistake.
I made a mistake in saying that I was at the front of the line.
Yes. Above all, the audience was warm.
The radio audience really makes you feel at home, and I'm grateful for that.
I hope that the audience will be able to get used to the large number of idol fans at this event and do their best.
I was really worried because I couldn't speak every time.
Well, you know.
But it was good to be able to say at least a few words of greeting and that we would go on like this.
It's not easy to say in such a situation.
But it was pretty good, wasn't it? It was a good thing, wasn't it?
Thank you, thank you. I hope you will continue to do your best little by little.
See you soon.
by H.
Thanks again for watching to the end.
How was today?
Hey, did you enjoy it?
What did you like?
Hey, tell me the truth.
I'm not mad at you. Just tell me the truth.
I'm not mad at you.
Yeah, I'm not mad.
Let me know what you think in the comments section or on Twitter.
In the comments section or on Twitter. Please.
Please.